export const QuizData = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: `Which type of Javscript language is _____?`,
        options: [`Object oriented `, `Object Based`, `Assembly-Language`, `High-Level`],
        answer: `High-Level`
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'The "Function" and "var" are known as :',
        options: ['Keywords', 'Data Types', 'Declaration Statements', 'Prototypes'],
        answer: 'Declaration Statements'
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question:'In javascript , which one of the following is not considered as an error :' ,
        options: ['Syntax error ', 'Missing of semicolons', 'Division by zero', 'Missing of bracket'],
        answer: 'Division by zero'
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question:'In javascript , which of the following number object function returns the value of the number ?',
        options: ['toString() ', 'valueOf()', 'toLocaleString()', 'toPrecision'],
        answer: 'valueOf()'
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question:  'In javascript , which of the following is an ternary operator ?',
        options: [' ? ',
        ':',
         '-',
         '+'],
        answer: ' ? '
    }, 
    {
        id: 5,
        question:  'In javascript , which of the following method or operator  is used for identification of the array ?',
        options: [' Typeof ',
        '==',
        '===',
        'isarrayType()'],
        answer: 'isarrayType()'
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question:'who is richest person in the world?'  ,
        options: ['Jeff Bezos', 
        'Elon Musk', 
         'Mukesh Ambani',
        'Warren Buffett'],
        answer:  'Elon Musk'
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question:'If a function which does not return a value is known as ________?',
        options: ['Static function',
        'Procedures',
        'Method ', 
         'Dynamic function'],
        answer: 'Procedures'
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'The execution of a function stops when the program control encounters the  ________statement in the body of the function ?',
        options: ['return statement',
        'continue statement ',
        'break staement',
        'goto statement '],
        answer: 'return statement'
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Which of the following type of a variable is volatile ?' ,
        options: ['Mutable variavle',
        'Dynamic variable',
        'Volatile variabale',
        'Immutable variable'],
        answer:'Mutable variavle'
    },
]